[{"answer": "How long you staying", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I mean, in the hotel", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I mean, in the hotel", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " I... I was just askin'", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Nope", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Ain't a man", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "He's a private detective.  I drive to L.A. now and then", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "He'll get us anything, for twenty bucks a day and expenses.  my friend, you worry too fast and too easy", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " About what?  What'll we talk to him about? The birds, the bees? The weather? The crops?  You tried", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Sure. You only thought", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't know. Maybe diamonds. Maybe gunpowder", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I thought the tradition of the old West was hospitality", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " You mean, because of your arm?  I knew a man once, lost an arm in a threshing accident. Used to hunt all the time.  But he was quite a man. He...  I'm sorry. I... What I mean is", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " You're looking for what, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " What did he want", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " A storm? About what", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " A storm? About what", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Trouble? You don't know anything about my friend, now do you, my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Trouble? You don't know anything about my friend, now do you, my friend", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "The point is, what you don't know can't hurt you", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend find himself a new boy. I can't take it another day.  If you're a sheriff, they gotta respect you, otherwise you can't do your job.  They just laugh", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Why don't you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It was, just a few hours ago", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Sure. And my friend is the kid who changes 'em", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Nothing. It's none of your concern", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Am I concerned", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I have a way with jeeps. A certain familiarity", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I think I understand. You're an that place man.  Where'd you get it", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Tough. I tried to get in myself, the day after those rats bombed that place", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Maybe I'm not so big", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What makes you mad, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What's funny", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " You don't seem to believe anything I say", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Don't look at me like that", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Like I'm a potential customer", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " Well, so long, my friend. I can't say it's been charming but..", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I don't know. But I'm going on foot", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " I'm sorry, son. You got to admit, I tried", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Maybe what", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " You're doing the best you can.  Aren't you, my friend", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Don't worry, I won't", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " Maybe I could have been something", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Well, I don't, really. I'm a dime a dozen", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes I do", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "That I don't believe", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "That I don't believe", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "It's never too late", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "You two started out in a car. That's the way you'll end up. Over a cliff, burning.  You can blame that on Macreedy, too. He said I had too many witnesses", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I got to start with somebody", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": " Am I going to have trouble with you", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": " Just as you took care of his buddies", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Nope. But I sure thought the situation was going to be like reversed. I thought I was going to have trouble...  ...with him. I'll take care of him", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Just as I took care of his buddies. Me, an' Doc, and my friend..", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "What's on your mind, my friend", "docId": "Bad-Day-at-Black-Rock.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "\"We...", "qsentId": 56}]